Guide to the Lincoln Steffens Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series III. Letters of Lincoln Steffens
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 January 5, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 January 6, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 January 6, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 January 14, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 January 22, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 January 27, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 February 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 February 13, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1927 February 13, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1927 February 13, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 February 16, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1927 February 23, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 February 24, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1927 February 24, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 March, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1927 March, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 March 2, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 March 5, (t.l., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 March 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 March 12, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1927 March 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1927 March 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1927 March 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 March 13, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 72)
    - To Ella Winter, 1927 March 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1927 March 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 March 28, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 March 31, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 April 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 April 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 May 8, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1927 May 9, (t.l.s., 2p., signed "Pete") (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 May 14, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 May 18, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.) and Allen H. Suggett, 1927 May 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 June 1, (a.l.s., 1p., with postscript by Ella Winter) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 June 5, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 June 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1927 June 7, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 June 10, (a.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1927 July 18, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 July 28, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 July 31, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 August 3, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 August 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 August 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 August 6-7, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 August 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), [1927] August 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 August 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 August 31, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 September, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 September 5, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 September 8, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 September 11, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 September 14, (a.l.s., 4p., with a note in the hand of Ella Winter) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 September 16, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 September 17, (a.l.s., 2p., with a note in the hand of Ella Winter) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 September 20, (a.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 September 20, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), circa 1927 October 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
  - Winter, Ella--To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 October 5, (a.l.s., 4p., enclosed with the above letter, with envelope) (Box 72)
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1927 October 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 October 14, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 October 17, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 October 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 October 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 October 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 October 29, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 November 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 November 6, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 November 12, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 November 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 November 28, (a.l.s., 3p., with envelope) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 December 1, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 December 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 December 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 December 18, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1927 December 19, (t.l.s.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 December 21, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 72)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1927 December 24, (t.l.s., 2p., with autograph postscript) (Box 72)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 January 1, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 January 3, (t.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 January 7, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1928 January 8, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett and Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 January 11, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1928 January 12, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 January 17, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 January 19, (a.l.s., 4p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 January 25, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 73)
  - Winter, Ella--To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 January 28, (a.l.s., 2p., enclosed with above letter, with envelope) (Box 73)
  - Steffens, Lincoln
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 January 29, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 February 1, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1928 February 10, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 February 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 February [15], (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1928 February 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 February 20, (a.l.s., 2p., torn) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 February 23, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 February [24], (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 February 28, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 February 29, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 March 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1928 March 5, (a.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1928 March 18, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 March 21, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 March [25], (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1928 March 28, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 March 30, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 April 1, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 April 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 April 7, (a.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 April 11, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 April 13, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1928 April 13, (t.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 April 18, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1928 April 18, (a.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 April 30, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 May 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 May 10, (a.l.s., 1p., with envelope) (Box 73)
    - To Allen H. Suggett, 1928 May 14-15, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 May 14-15, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 May 18, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 May 21, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 May 25, (t.l.s., 1p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 May 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 June 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 June 8, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1928 September 13, (t.l.s., 5p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 October 31, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 October 31, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 November, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 November 5, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 November 7, (a.l.s., 6p., with partial typed transcript) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 November 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 November 11, (a.l., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 November 16, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1928 November 19, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1928 November 21, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Laura Steffens Suggett (2nd Mrs. Allen H.), 1929 March 2, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Jane B. Hollister, 1929 June 10, (t.l. copy, 1p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1929 June 12, (t.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 June 27, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 June 28, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 June 28, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 June 30, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 1, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 2, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 2, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 5, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 6, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July [9], (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 10, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 13, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 15, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 16, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To [Ella Winter], 1929 July 18, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 21, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1929 July 21, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 73)
    - To Pete Stanley Steffens, circa 1929 July 22, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July [23], (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 25, (a.l., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 26, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 27, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 28, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Pete Stanley Steffens, 1929 July 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 July 31, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 6, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 7, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 9-10, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 12, (a.l., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 12, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1929 August 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Pete Stanley Steffens, 1929 August 14, (a.l.s., 4p., postscript to Ella Winter) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 15-16, (a.l., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Pete Stanley Steffens, 1929 August 17, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 19-20, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 22, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 23, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Pete Stanley Steffens, 1929 August 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 26, (a.l., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 27, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 August 31, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 3, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 73)
    - To Pete Stanley Steffens, 1929 September 4, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 4, (a.l., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 7, (a.l., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 8, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Pete Stanley Steffens, 1929 September 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 9, (a.l., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 10, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 13, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1929 September 14, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1929 September 17, (t.l.s., 3p., with note in the hand of Ella Winter) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1929 September 17, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 19, (t.l.s., 2p., with autograph postscript) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 20, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 21-23, (a.l.s., 8p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 22, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, [1929] September [24], (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 26, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To E.A. [Filene], 1929 September 26, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 September 27, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1929 September 28, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1929 October 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1929 October 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 October 5-12, (a.l., 8p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 October 14, (a.l.s., 2p., damaged, torn, with purple ink blots) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 October 15, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 October 17, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 October 20, (a.l.s.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 October 24, (t.l.s., 4p.) (Box 73)
    - To Ella Winter, 1929 October 27, (a.l.s., 7p.) (Box 73)
    - To Allen Griffin, 1930 March 29, (t.l., copy, 1p.) (Box 74)
    - To Committee of Admissions, the Players Club, 1930 April 22, (ms.l., 2p.) (Box 74)
      (Letter recommending Ernest Hemmingway for admission, in the hand of Ella Winter)
    - To Ella Winter, circa 1930 July, (a.l., 1p., part of letter dictated by Pete Stanley Steffens) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, circa 1930 July, (a.l.s., 2p., fragment, last two pages only of a longer letter) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 5, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 6-7, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 7-9, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July [11], (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 12-14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 14, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 15, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, [1930] July 16-17, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 18, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 24, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 July 28?, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 1, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 1, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August? 2-4, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 5, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 6, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 8, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 10, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 11?, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 12, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 16, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 18, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 27, (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August 27, (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 August [29], (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 September 1, (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 September 7, (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 September 7, (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 September? 8, (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 December 22, (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter and Pete Stanley Steffens, 1930 December 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1930 December 27, (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1931 February 16, (t.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To [Edward J.] Bernays, 1931 April 14, (a.l.s., facsimile) (Box 74)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1931 April 30, (a.l.s.) (Box 74)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1931 May 30, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 74)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1931 July 17, (t.l., 2p., signed by Pete Stanley Steffens with a note in his hand) (Box 74)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1931 July 25, (t. and a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 August 30, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 September 2, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 September 9, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 September 17, (a.l.s., 6p.) (Box 74)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1931 September 21, (t.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 September 24, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 September 27, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1931 October 1, (a.l.s., 1p.) (Box 74)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1931 October 25, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1931 November 1, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1931 November 8, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Anna [McCarthy], 1931 November 22, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Dot Steffens Hollister (Mrs. John James), 1931 November 23, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 10, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 12, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 14, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 15, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 20, (a.l.s., 3p., with two-page letter to Ella Winter in the hand of Lincoln Steffens, signed by Pete Stanley Steffens) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 22, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 26, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 29, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1931 December 30, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, [1932], (a.l.s., 2p., last page only of a longer letter, drawing and note by Pete Stanley Steffens on verso) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1932 January 3, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1932 January 5, (a.l.s., 5p.) (Box 74)
    - To [Lena] Hughes, 1932 January 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1932 January 7, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1932 February [28], (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, circa 1932 March?, (a.l.s., 1p., last page only of a longer letter) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1932 March 11, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1932 March 17, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 74)
    - To Elizabeth Nixon Winstanley, 1932 April 6, (ms.l., 1p., copy in unknown hand) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1932 May 1, (a.l.s., 2p., with envelope) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1932 June 20, (a.l.s., 2p.) (Box 74)
    - To Ella Winter, 1932 June 21, (a.l.s., 3p.) (Box 74)
    - To Mrs. A. (Frieda) Winter, 1932 August 10, (a.l.s., 4p.) (Box 74)